

# Romi Ramadhan

Date of birth: February 22, 1993

## **Contact Details**

Home: 021-831-3515 Cell: 0821-237-08169 ramadhanromi34@gmail.com Setiabudi, South Jakarta, 12970

### **Personal Skills**

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Transferable skill
- · Flexibility
- · Interpersonal skill
- Adaptability
- · Willingness to learn
- Patience

## **Personal Profile**

Experienced Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the leading Mobile Content & Service Provider. Skilled in Spring Boot, Databases, Java, Spring Framework, React JS, JQuery and Core Java. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Electrical Engineering from Gunadarma University.

# **Specializations**

- Reading Wiring Diagram
- Setting, Troubleshooting & Calibration
- Java Programming (Spring Boot)
- Thymeleaf & Pebble Template
- PLC Siemens S7-1200 & HMI KTP 400
- English Conversation (TOEFL PBT: 497)
- JQuery, React JS & SQL Server
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel & Power Point)

## **Career Summary**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

PT. Triyakom April 2021 - Present

- Develop system applications to support business process.
- Maintain and enhance system applications.
- Perform testing for system applications.
- Troubleshoot and debug applications.
- Make database queries needed in the development process.
- Make improvements and or adding features to existing applications.

#### HARDWARE ENGINEER

PT. Number Oner Perso January 2018 - April 2021

- Assisted in operating, maintaining and troubleshooting card machine.
- Editing photo.
- Assisted in packaging and checking printed cards.
- Making daily report.
- Support another division if there is a problem.

# **Training Summary**

Udemy (2021 Complete Python Bootcamp From Zero to Hero) February 2021 - Present

- Learn to started webscraping.
- Learn to working with image, email, and CSV file

BBPLK CEVEST (Industrial Electronics and Automation)

October 2015 - December 2015

- Installing relay sequence controller.
- Wiring motor control DOL, FW/BW, Star-Delta connection.
- Applying pneumatics and electro-pneumatics system.
- Operating PLC Mitsubishi.

# **Academic Background**

#### **GUNADARMA UNIVERSITY**

March 2014 to December 2015 M.S. in Electrical Engineering GPA 3.53

#### **GUNADARMA UNIVERSITY**

September 2010 to February 2014 B.S. in Telecommunication GPA 3.60

66

You don't hire for skills, you hire for attitude. you can always teach skills.